GAYATHRI J

Adoor, Kerala | https://www.linkedin.com/in/gayathrij2003 | gayathrij263@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

Computer Science and Engineering student with a desire of internship role in an organization where I use my analytical thinking and build a valuable skill set. Comes with exceptional ability to work and learn at the same time to gain experience and knowledge about the system.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science and Engineering Sree Buddha College of Engineering, Pattoor. CGPA-8.58	2021-Present
Higher Secondary Education in Science NSS HSS Choorakode, Adoor. Percentage-98.9%	2019-2021
High School Education(Class X) Vivekananda HS For Girls, Kadampanad. Grade- A+	2018-2019

EXPERIENCE

Secretary

IEEE Computer Society of Sree Buddha College of Engineering, Pattoor Feb 2024-Present

Newsletter Editor

IEEE Student Branch of Sree Buddha College of Engineering, Pattoor Feb 2023-Mar 2024

SKILLS

- C programming
- MySQL
- Java
- Python

- HTML
- Machine Learning
- Data Science
- MS Office-PowerPoint, Word

CERTIFICATIONS

NPTEL - Soft Skills

NPTEL Certification for Soft skills with a consolidated score of 81% along with silver badge

NPTEL - Python for Data Science

NPTEL Certification for Python using Data Science with a consolidated score of 65%

Machine Learning with TensorFlow

Completed Tech labs Initiative-Machine Learning with TensorFlow by DeepLearning.AI associated with ICT academy of Kerala

Developers - Android with Compose

Completed Tech labs Initiative-Android with Compose by Developers associated with ICT academy of Kerala